Priyanka Bose

Security Researcher, SecLab, UCSB ⊠ priyanka@cs.ucsb.edu

¹¹ pbose.in

in c1nderella

У cinderella0x80

⊕ priyankabose

Research Interests

My research interest is in the domain of systems, software security, and decentralized finance (DeFi). Specifically, I develop program analysis techniques to discover vulnerabilities in real-world applications, such as, but not limited to blockchain, smart contracts and Android apps.

Education

2016-Present	Ph.D. , <i>University of California</i> , Santa Barbara, <i>GPA – 4.0/4.0</i> .
	Computer Security, advised by Giovanni Vigna & Christopher Kruegel

2016–2022 **MS**, *University of California*, Santa Barbara, *GPA – 4.0/4.0*. Computer Security, advised by Giovanni Vigna & Christopher Kruegel

2013–2015 **MS**, *Indian Institute of Technology*, Madras, *GPA – 9.0/10.0*. Computer Science & Engineering, advised by PanduRangan Chandrasekaran

2007–2011 **B.Tech.**, *Institute of Engineering & Management*, Kolkata, *GPA – 9.05/10.0*. Computer Science & Engineering

Professional Experience

2016-Present Graduate Student Researcher, University of California, Santa Barbara, Santa Barbara.

2015–2016 **Post-Graduate Research Intern**, School of Computing (SoC), National University of Singapore (NUS), Singapore.

2013–2015 **Teaching Assistant**, *Indian Institute of Technology (IIT)*, Madras.

2011–2013 **Systems Engineer**, *Infosys Limited*, Bhubaneswar.

Publications

- [7] **P. Bose**, D. Das, S. Vasan, S. Mariani, I. Grishchenko, A. Continella, A. Bianchi, C. Kruegel, and G. Vigna, "Columbus: Android App Testing Through Systematic Callback Exploration," in *(Under Submission)*, 2023.
- [6] **P. Bose**, D. Das, Y. Chen, Y. Feng, C. Kruegel, and G. Vigna, "Sailfish: Vetting Smart Contract State-Inconsistency Bugs in Seconds," in *IEEE Symposium on Security and Privacy (IEEE S&P)*, 2022.
- [5] D. Das, **P. Bose**, A. Machiry, S. Mariani, Y. Shoshitaishvili, C. Kruegel, and G. Vigna, "Hybrid Pruning: Towards Precise Pointer and Taint Analysis," in *Detection of Intrusions and Malware and Vulnerability Assessment (DIMVA)*, 2022.
- [4] D. Das, **P. Bose**, N. Ruaro, C. Kruegel, and G. Vigna, "Understanding Security Issues in the NFT Ecosystem," in *Conference on Computer and Communications Security (CCS)*, 2022.
- [3] D. Meng, M. Guerriero, A. Machiry, H. Aghakhani, **P. Bose**, A. Continella, C. Kruegel, and G. Vigna, "Bran: Reduce Vulnerability Search Space in Large Open Source Repositories by Learning Bug Symptoms," in *ACM Asia Conference on Computer and Communications Security (ASIA CCS)*, 2021.
- [2] **P. Bose**, V. T. Hoang, and S. Tessaro, "Revisiting AES-GCM-SIV: Multi-user Security, Faster Key Derivation, and Better Bounds," in *Advances in Cryptology (EUROCRYPT)*, 2018.
- [1] **P. Bose**, D. Das, and C. P. Rangan, "Constant Size Ring Signature Without Random Oracle," in *Australasian Conference on Information Security and Privacy (ACISP)*, 2015.

Ongoing Research Projects

NFT-MEV

Analyzing trading activities of Non-Fungible tokens (NFT) to understand diverse market manipulation strategies adapted by the traders to maximize their profits.

Academic Presentations

Conference presentation

Sailfish: Vetting Smart Contract State-Inconsistency Bugs in Seconds, IEEE Symposium on Security and Privacy (IEEE S&P), May 2022.

Professional Activities

- o Reported 6 high-impact security vulnerabilities with financial consequences in OpenSea, Sorare, and Rarible marketplaces (2021).
- o Contributed to *Slither*, a popular smart contract static analyzer by Trail of Bits.
- o Member of Shellphish Capture-The-Flag (CTF) team. Participated in DEFCON CTF Finals in the year 2019.
- o Member of Women in Cybersecurity (WiCyS), UCSB Chapter.
- o Guest speaker at Career Panel for Women in Cybersecurity (WiCyS), UCSB Chapter.

Awards / Achievements

- Received scholarship to attend Grace Hopper Celebration'18.
- Selected for attending RSA Security Scholar Program'18.
- Entitled to Presidential Graduate Fellowship (PGF) at National University of Singapore (NUS).
- o Received scholarship for two years (2013 2015) from Ministry of Human Resource and Development (MHRD), Government of India for higher studies at IIT, Madras.
- o Received National Merit Scholarship from Ministry of Human Resource and Development (MHRD), Government of India for 66^{th} position in state in X^{th} standard board examination.
- o Secured All-India Rank 657 among 2, 24, 160 candidates in GATE 2013.
- o Secured All-India Rank 1196 among 87,163 candidates in West Bengal Joint Entrance Examination 2007 (Engineering).

Media Coverage

Axetue, OpenSea hack verified 3 security concerns. Here's what you need to know, (Feb 2022).

Hong Kong Security Response Team Coordinate Centre (HKCERT), What You Know about the Cyber Security of NFT, (Mar 2022).

Medium, NFT Security 101, (Mar 2022).

Sensors Tech Forum, NFT Security and Risks: How Secure Are Your Digital Assets?, (Feb 2022).

Merehead, How to make NFTs secure?, (Dec 2021).

CoinYuppie, Do you know how to audit safe and reliable NFT projects?, (Feb 2022).

DevNews Podcast, Elon Musk's Twitter Takeover, Security Vulnerabilities in Web3, and Experimenting With the TikTok Algorithm, (Apr 2022).

The Atlantic, Please Ignore My Last 577 Tweets, (May 2022).

TruthDAO Podcast, NFT Academic Roundtable, (May 2022).

TruthDAO, Fraudulent "Wash Sales" Roil Booming NFT Market, (May 2022).

TruthDAO, Fake Trading, Stablecoin Troubles, and the Threat of Crypto Regulation: Our Crypto DeFined NFT Roundtable Takeaways, (May 2022).

Sailfish [6] TheHackerNews, SAILFISH System to Find State-Inconsistency Bugs in Smart Contracts, (Jan 2022).

IEMLabs, SAILFISH System to Find State-Inconsistency Bugs in Smart Contracts, (Jan 2022).

CyberFishNews, SAILFISH System to Find State-Inconsistency Bugs in Smart Contracts, (Jan 2022).

CyberSecurity.News, SAILFISH System to Find State-Inconsistency Bugs in Smart Contracts, (Jan 2022).

NFT Study [4]